B.Tech. Computer Science Engineering

Name – Vrushit Patel Date of Birth – 17th January 2000



OBJECTIVE

Always been eager to learn and develop more skills. I have been coding for the last 6 years and proficient in C++, Java, Python. Have attained a good practice in Web Development - Full Stack. Experienced in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL and Django.

EDUCATION

Degree	Institute	Board/University	Year	Performance
B.Tech.	NMIMS, MPSTME	NMIMS University	Currently Pursuing 4 th Year	3.8 / 4.00 CGPA Till date
12th	Chatrabhuj Narsee Memorial School	ISC	2018	88.6%
10th	Chatrabhuj Narsee Memorial School	ICSE	2016	85.5%

TECHNICAL SKILLS

	Familiar with			
C, C++,Java, Python				
Detailed understanding of computer hardware and their connectivity.				
Expert at Problem Solving.				
Experienced at coding on Arduino Platform.				
Expert in Full Sta	ack Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, My	vSOL Firebase and	Diango	

WORK EXPERIENCE				
Software Workshop Technologies Pvt. Ltd	OpenCV Software Intern : Worked on OpenCV projects in Python analyzing videos and photographs from CCTV, both recorded and real-			
(04/2021 - 06/2021)	time.			
(3 Months)				

KEY PROJECTS / PRESENTATION/ SEMINARS/ WORKSHOPS			
Bar Stock Exchange Dine-in Ordering (03/2021 - 04/2021)	Bar Stock Exchange is a dine-in ordering software implementing a stock market theme. This software implements Dynamic and Asynchronous features.		
Implement Level 2 Of Self Driving In GTA V ((08/2020 - 09/2020)	Implement Self Driving Till Level 2 using Image Processing in which it detects nearby objects and lane detection in a game called GTA V . It informs the driver to stop or if any signboard is nearby.		
Med-Bay Website (09/2020 - 10/2020)	Made a website for searching doctors and hospital nearby. Implemented HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX and PHP . Full Dynamic Website with login and posting blogs features.		
Made 3 Website For College Festival (12/2020 - 03/2021)	Was part of 3 College Festival, in which lead 2 as a Sub-Head and build them custom themed websites. Used Django as our back-end and HTML, CSS, JavaScript for fronted-end.		

B.Tech. Computer Science Engineering

Name – Vrushit Patel Date of Birth – 17th January 2000



EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

- I have taken part in **Hack-N-Code 4.0 Hackathon** (03/2021), and was the **First Runner Up.**
- Detailed understanding of computer hardware and their connectivity. I have also assembled a computer.
- Social Conclave MPSTME: Sub-head of Technical Department.
- Tagneeq 13.0 MPSTME: **Sub-head of Technical Department**.
- Sattva MPSTME: Executive of Technical Department.
- ACM: Executive of Technical Department.
- Some Skills:
 - o Also have good understanding of Git & Git-Hub.
 - o Experienced in Adobe Photoshop & Premier Pro.

CORE COMPETENCY:

- → Problem Solving
- → Leadership
- → Teamwork
- → Communication
- → Time Management
- → Critical Thinking